Whoa. &gt;&gt; High five,
哇 — 击个掌
our students are showing some real developer chops now.
我们的学生正在展示 真正的开发者才能
&gt;&gt; Yeah, super exciting.
— 是的 我很高兴
Wait, Joe not to be a party pooper,
虽然不想扫兴 但是 Joe
but did you tell the students about the gotcha with AsyncTask?
你告诉过学生关于 AsyncTask 的理解吗？
&gt;&gt; No, why can't we just celebrate?
— 没有 为什么我们不庆贺一番？
&gt;&gt; Dude, we really need to tell them.
— 我们真的需要告诉他们
&gt;&gt; Fine, you tell them.
— 好吧 你来告诉他们
&gt;&gt; Okay, let's think about what happens when I open up the app and
— 好 让我们想一想 当打开应用并
launch the earthquake activity.
启动地震活动时会发生什么
At this point, we have an activity object in memory.
这时 内存中有一个活动对象
Then in the onCreate method, we instantiate a new AsyncTask object.
然后 我们在 onCreate 方法中 实例化新的 AsyncTask 对象
Which then starts running on a background thread and
该对象之后会在 后台线程中开始运行
opens up an HTTP connection.
并打开 HTTP 连接
Now here's the catch, before the AsyncTask finishes,
现在重点来了 在 AsyncTask 完成前
what happens if I rotate my phone?
如果我旋转手机会发生什么？
Well, in order to show our UI properly in the new orientation,
为了在新的方向上 正确显示我们的 UI
the system needs to create a new activity and relayout our views.
系统需要创建新的活动 并重新布局我们的视图
And since memory is limited on a mobile device, this also means that the system
由于移动设备的内存有限 这意味着系统可能
probably should destroy the old activity and reclaim the memory it occupied.
需要销毁旧的活动 并回收所占用的内存
But since the AsyncTask is an inner class of the original activity,
但由于 AsyncTask 是 原始活动的内部类
that memory can't be reclaimed until the AsyncTask is finished executing.
所以在 AsyncTask 停止 执行前 无法回收其内存
Let me explain what I mean.
让我来解释一下这是什么意思
Note that any time our phone is rotated,
请注意 每次旋转手机时
a new activity gets created from scratch.
都会从头创建 一个新的活动
And via our code, so does a new AsyncTask instance.
并通过代码 创建新的 AsyncTask 实例
It starts another background thread and opens up another HTTP connection.
AsyncTask 将启动另一个后台 线程并打开另一个 HTTP 连接
Now this is very wasteful because now there's actually AsyncTask.
但由于实际上已经存在 AsyncTask 这是非常浪费的
And two in closing activities residing in memory at the same time,
最后会在内存中同时 保留两个活动
twice as much as before.
这是之前的两倍
So what happens when the first AsyncTask finally completes?
所以 当第一个 AsyncTask 最终完成时会发生什么？
Well, the result of the task is no longer useful
由于屏幕中 不再显示视图
because the views are no longer shown on the screen.
所以任务结果 将不可用
Which is kind of a waste of device resources.
这是一种对设备 资源的浪费
Fetching and parsing a server response that will never be seen, right?
获取并解析不再可见 的服务器响应 对吗？
But what if we rotate the phone multiple times?
但如果多次 旋转手机呢？
Now we've got a ton of extra AsyncTask and
我们将得到大量的 多余 AsyncTask
activities in memory trying to run and talk to the network at once.
内存中的活动立即 尝试运行并连接到网络
As a result, we use all of this additional memory unnecessarily,
因此 我们使用了所有 不必要的额外内存
possibly even slowing down our phone.
这可能拖慢我们的手机
While we only really need one activity and one AsyncTask for
我们实际上只需要 屏幕上目前显示的
what's currently being displayed on the screen.
一个活动和 一个 AsyncTask
Plus, if you really think about it,
另外 如果认真想一想
all of these new tasks will likely receive the same result.
所有这些新任务很可能 都收到相同的结果
Because there's probably not much earthquake data changing
因为在我们旋转 手机的几秒内
during the few seconds we were rotating the phone.
地震数据可能 不会有太多变化
So ideally, anytime we create a new activity to support an orientation
所以实际上 我们每次 创建新的任务来支持
change, it would be more efficient if we just use the original result from that
方向改变不如使用 第一个 HTTP 请求中
first HTTP request.
的原始结果有效
Provided that it completed successfully of course.
当然 前提是 可以成功完成
Instead, we have multiple network requests in flight to the same server.
然而 我们向同一服务器 发出了多个网络请求
All fetching and parsing the same response.
这些请求都获取 并解析同一响应
Super wasteful, yuck.
这太浪费了
&gt;&gt; Okay, Chris, you're scaring the student now.
— 很好 Chris 你现在 吓到了学生们
There's got to be a better way.
其实还有一种更好的方法
&gt;&gt; In fact, there is.
— 的确
&gt;&gt; Watch the Android performance pattern video we've linked below and
— 观看下面链接的 Android 运行模式视频
then answer this quiz question.
并回答测验问题
On what component in Android helps us solve this issue?
Android 中的哪部分可以 帮助我们解决这个问题？